[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 7) \u00d7 (9 - 4)?",
      "correctAnswer": "55",
      "options": [
        "57",
        "56",
        "54",
        "55"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 5) \u00d7 (10 - 4)?",
      "correctAnswer": "54",
      "options": [
        "55",
        "53",
        "56",
        "54"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 5) \u00d7 (6 - 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "24",
      "options": [
        "23",
        "26",
        "24",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 7) \u00d7 (6 - 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "-30",
      "options": [
        "-29",
        "-30",
        "-31",
        "-28"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 1) \u00d7 (10 - 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "28",
      "options": [
        "27",
        "29",
        "30",
        "28"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 1) \u00d7 (9 - 7)?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "17",
        "18",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 9) \u00d7 (1 - 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "-119",
      "options": [
        "-118",
        "-117",
        "-120",
        "-119"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 7) \u00d7 (8 - 4)?",
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "options": [
        "43",
        "44",
        "46",
        "45"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 2) \u00d7 (6 - 2)?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "18",
        "17",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 7) \u00d7 (7 - 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "-15",
      "options": [
        "-16",
        "-14",
        "-13",
        "-15"
      ]
    }
]